Hume先生
Mr. Hume.
我叫Zoe
My name is Zoe.
我知道您还不清醒
I know you're disoriented.
您昏迷了三天
You've been unconsciousness for the last three days.
但现在 全身麻醉的药效过了
But you're off the I.V. Sedation now.
我还帮您打了一针 有助您醒转
And I've just given you a shot to help you wake up.
你是护士?
Are you a nurse?
您现在没在医院了 Hume先生
You're not in a hospital anymore, Mr. Hume.
我们替您办了转院手续
We had to move you.
什么? 转... 转院? 转去哪儿了?
What? Move... move me? Move me where?
我妻子呢?
Where's my wife?
别动 先生... 您不能... 不能...
No. Wait. Mr... you shouldn't... you shouldn't...
我要见Penny
I wanna see Penny.
恐怕不行 Desmond
I'm afraid that's not gonna be possible, Desmond.
是你
You.
Hume先生...
Mr. Hume...
- 别紧张 别紧张 这儿有我  - 您得坐着啊
- Easy. Easy. I'll take it from here.  - You should sit.
Desmond啊
Desmond.
我怎么了? 我在哪?
What happened to me? Where am I?
你被Benjamin Linus打中了
You were shot by Benjamin Linus.
还记得吗?
Do you remember that?
嗯 记得
Yes, I remember.
我有话要跟Penny说 Penny!
Yeah, I wanna talk to Penny. Penny!
她不在这儿 但我向你担保
She's not here. But I assure you,
她和你儿子 都安然无恙
both she and your son are perfectly safe.
很抱歉把你们分开
I'm really sorry for taking you away from them,
但我没机会解释 而且...
but I didn't have a chance to explain, and...
如果我解释的话 你就不会跟我走了
if I had, you never would've come with me.
跟你走?
Come with you?
跟你去哪儿?
Come with you where?
我带你回到了这个岛上
I brought you back to the island.
我... 难以想象你的感受
I... can't imagine how you must be feeling.
但如果 你愿意让我解释一下的话...
But if you'll give me a chance to explain...
- 该死的! 别伤害他!  - 你居然把我弄回来了!
- Damn it! Don't hurt him!  - You take me back!
- 你居然把我又弄回来了!?  - 不是我把你弄回来的
- You take me back right now, you hear!?  - I can't take you back.
是这个岛 与你还有牵扯
The island isn't done with you yet.
啊!
Aah!
要Desmond来这儿干嘛?
What is Desmond doing here?
可意会
It will be easier for me
而不可言传 Kwon先生
to show you than to tell you, Mr. Kwon.
你带他去发电机房吧
Take him with you to the generator room.
我带着Hume一道 准备开始做试验
I'll be along with Hume so we can start the test.
Charles 那... 那... 那个试验 安排在明天
Charles, that... that... that test isn't scheduled till tomorrow.
我知道时间安排 现在就去准备妥当
I know when it's scheduled. Get them ready now.
跟上 没时间给你参观
Come on. No time for sightseeing.
他们直接带Hume过来了
They're bringing Hume down now.
- 什么?!  - 你听得很清楚 我们走吧
- What?!  - You heard me. We are go right now.
- 你这边准备得如何 Frame?  - 我们根本就没准备好
- What's your time Frame?  - We're not even close to being ready.
这台发电机 搞不好20年没运行过了
This generator probably hasn't run in 20 years.
- 我怎么可能...  - Widmore等不了了
- How am I supposed to...  - Widmore doesn't want to wait.
- 你来这儿干嘛?  - 做个小测试
- What are you doing here?  - Running a little test.
- 什么测试?  - 好吧 看看我们的进度如何
- What kind of test?  - All right, let's see where we are.
- 各位 能把磁场运作起来吗?  - 没问题
- Can we get a functioning M. Field going, people?  - Sure thing.
- 我们做个电力测试 发电机全速运转  - 收到
- Let's try a power test. Generator to full, please.  - Okay.
搞定
Okay.
准备 听我指令...
Here we go. On my count...
三... 二... 一
Three... Two... One.
启动
And power on.
见鬼
Great.
肯定哪里接错了 快把问题搞清楚
We probably got a faulty contact somewhere. Find it.
Simmons 去查查螺线管的电路
Simmons, go down and check the circuits on the solenoids.
- 遵命  - 再试试
- Yes, sir.  - Try it again.
知道吗 Angstrom?
Guess what, Angstrom?
下一个就轮到你了
You're going in there next.
搞清楚了!
Found it!
是发电机的断路器坏了
It's a bad breaker on the genny.
- 马上接上  - 别!
- Bringing it back online now.  - No!
不要!
No!
关掉! 快关掉!
Turn it off! Turn it off!
Zoe啊
Zoe.
- 弄好了吗?  - 带他过来
- Are we ready?  - Let's go.
迷失 第6季第11集
停
Stop.
把他抬走吧 谢谢
You can take him now. Thank you.
把他拉进去
Put him inside.
不! 嘿! 你们到底要干什么?!
No! Hey! What the hell are you doing?!
啊! 啊!
Uhh! Aah!
- 我知道这看上去很可怕 Desmond  - 啊!
- I know how this looks, Desmond.  - Aah!
但如果之前我听到的 你的那些事 都确有其事
But if everything I've been told about you is true,
你会安然无恙的
you'll be perfectly fine.
你身上没金属物品吧? 比如钥匙? 零钱?
You don't have any metal on you, do you? Keys? Change?
肯定没有 笨蛋
Of course he doesn't, you idiot.
我不想强迫你 Desmond...
I hate to resort to forcing this upon you, Desmond...
但等这事结束后
But once it's over,
我希望你能做个牺牲
I'm going to ask you to make a sacrifice.
我相信 为了我们大家 你会帮我的
And I hope, for all our sakes, you'll help me.
牺牲?
Sacrifice?
你到底晓不晓得啥叫牺牲?
What the bloody hell do you know about sacrifice?
我儿子为了这个岛 死在这儿
My son died here for the sake of this island.
你妻子... 我的亲生女儿...
Your wife...  my own daughter...
恨我入骨
hates me.
我连外孙的面都没见过
And I've never even met my grandson.
如果你不帮我 Desmond
But if you won't help me, Desmond,
那就等着一切灰飞烟灭吧
all of it will be for nothing.
Penny 你儿子 还有其他人
Penny, your son and everyone else
都会... 死
will be gone... forever.
啊!
Aah!
Uhh!
啊!
Aah!
好了 启动吧
All right. Turn it on.
不 如果你想让我帮你做事
No. If you want me to help you with whatever you're doing here,
你必须先向我解释...
you need to explain to me...
我只知道那个人 是全世界唯一一个
That man is the only person I'm aware of in the world
在电磁灾难中 幸存下来的人
who has survived a catastrophic electromagnetic event.
我得弄清楚 他是否可以再次安然脱险
I need to know that he can do it again,
否则我们就只有死路一条
or we all die.
启动
Turn it on.
- 拉至最大马力了吗?  - 嗯 但...
- Do we have full power?  - Yeah, but...
放我出去!
Let me out!
放我出去 你们这些混蛋!
Let me out of here, you bastards!
放我出去!
Let me out!
Let me out of here!
放我出去!
大洋航空
在4号行李传送带
It's Carousel 4.
你说什么?
Sorry?
你乘坐悉尼航班来的 对吗?
You were on the Sydney flight, right?
- 没错  - 我们的行李在4号传送带
- Yeah.  - Our bags are on Carousel 4.
我向柜台那伙计 反复确认过了
I double-checked it with the dude at the counter.
谢谢你
Thank you.
稳住 我来拿 我帮你拿
Hang on. I've got it. I got it.
太感谢了
Thank you so much.
不客气
Pleasure.
你还有其它行李吗?
Do you have any more bags?
没有 呃 只有这一个 谢天谢地
No. Uh, that's it, thank God.
- 怀着男孩 还是女孩?  - 呃...
- Boy or a girl?  - Um...
- 哦 抱歉 我... 我... 我无意探人隐私  - 哦 别 别这样说 没... 关系的
- Oh, I'm sorry. I... I... I didn't mean to pry.  - Oh, no, no. It's... it's fine.
我只是 呃... 不知道是男是女
I just, um... I don't know what it is.
哦 明白
Oh, right.
你比我勇敢多了 我可没勇气忐忑地等到孩子出生
Well, you're braver than I. I'm not a big fan of surprises.
哦 抱歉 这是我的行李
Oh, excuse me. That's mine.
那么... 有... 有人来接你吗?
So... have... have you got someone meeting you?
啊 有的 我... 我也搞不清 或许他们...
Uh, yeah. I... I don't know. Maybe they got the...
搞错了航班 或出了其它纰漏
Flights mixed up or something.
之所以这么问 是因为我有车来接
Because I've got a car picking me up.
如果你想搭个便车
You know, if you need a ride,
我乐意效劳
I'd be more than happy to give you a lift.
哦 不 不 不 真是谢谢你了
Oh, no, no, no. That's, um, that's really sweet of you,
- 不过 我... 没事 还有出租车嘛 所以...  - 哦 哦 明白了
- But I'm... I'm good. There's cabs, so...  - Oh. Oh, all right. Yeah.
- 嗯 很高兴认识你  - 彼此彼此
- Well, it was nice meeting you.  - Yeah, nice to meet you, too.
是个儿子哦
A boy.
- 什么?  - 我肯定你怀的是个儿子
- What?  - I bet it's a boy.
... 储物柜位于行李问询处
... Lockers located at Baggage Claim Entrance.
行李问询处的具体位置 在...
Detailed baggage claim information on...
你等的人 似乎是我
Looks like I'm with you.
Hume先生 您好 我帮您拎行李吧
Mr. Hume. Hello. Let me grab that for you.
谢谢
Thank you.
- 我叫George  - 你好 George
- My name is George.  - Hi, George.
那接下来 要我带您去宾馆吗?
So I will take you back to your hotel?
去办公室吧
The office.
办公室 没问题 呃 请走这边
Office. Wonderful. Um, this way, please.
那么 呃 您... 是从悉尼乘飞机来的?
So, uh, you... you flew in from Sydney, huh?
嗯 没错
Yeah. That's right.
那么您... 您到澳洲 呃...
And what... what were you doin', uh....
做什么呢?
Down Under?
我去帮老板搞定一桩生意
I was closing a deal for the boss.
哦 真不错 祝贺您
Oh. Good for you. Congratulations.
嘿 我说 如果您在城里
Hey, listen, if you need anything at all
需要帮忙 请一定来找我
while you're in town, I know everyone.
比如需要预订房间 或挑选餐馆之类
If you need a reservation, you just pick a restaurant.
呃 宾馆的客房服务 会无微不至的
Uh, the Room Service at the hotel is excellent.
谢谢你
Thank you.
您 呃
You, uh,
您想要 呃 找个伴儿么?
you looking, uh, for some company?
呃 我看到您没戴婚戒
Well, I noticed that you weren't wearing a wedding band,
本地有很多美女
and there are a lot of lovely ladies
乐意提供 呃 "伴侣"服务
offering their, uh, "companionship."
我不想找人来陪
I'm not looking for any companionship.
我是来工作的
I'm here to work.
难怪您能成为老板的得力助手
Guess that's why you're e boss's right-hand man,
而我只是个司机
and I am the driver.
好 明白了
Okay. Got it.
- 早上好 Hume先生 一路顺风么?  - 平安无事 谢谢你
- Good morning, Mr. Hume. How was your flight?  - Lovely, thank you.
- 他说 让您直接进去就好  - 谢谢你
- He said to send you right in.  - Thank you.
Charles啊
Charles.
你好 Desmond
Hello, Desmond.
朋友 欢迎来到洛杉矶
Welcome to Los Angeles, my friend.
谢谢
Thank you.
我才不管他做了什么
I don't give a bloody damn what he did
或者要花多少钱
or how much it's going to cost.
等他受完审 把他弄出来就好
Just get him arraigned and get him out of there.
抱歉 Desmond
Sorry, Desmond.
貌似我们澳洲这笔交易的庆祝会
Looks like our celebration of the Australian deal
要缩短了
is gonna have to be cut short.
你知道我儿子是个音乐家吧?
You are aware that my son is a musician?
嗯 我听说他极具天赋
Yes. I've heard he's quite talented.
嗯 的确是这样
Yeah, he is, quite.
总之 我妻子在筹划
Anyway, my wife is putting together
一个慈善活动
one of her charity events,
然后 呃 那孩子异想天开
and, uh, the boy had the crazy idea
想把古典音乐和现代摇滚 合二为一
to combine classical music with modern rock.
你听过一个叫"驱动轴"的乐队吗?
Have you heard of a band called Drive Shaft?
呃 没听过
No can't say I have.
他们的贝斯手因为吸毒 呃 被捕了
Their bass guitarist overdosed and, uh, got himself arrested.
可是现在 如果我不把这个瘾君子 弄去参加我妻子的慈善活动
And now if I don't get this junkie to my wife's event,
她会 说白点儿就是 跟我没完
she will, simply put, destroy me.
- 所以 你想让我照看他  - 我知道这让你大材小用了
- So you want me to babysit him.  - I know it's beneath you,
但我需要某个我信任的人 去做这事
but I need someone I can trust to do the job right.
不用多说了 Charles 我会帮你的
Say no more, Charles. It's done.
你过的这才叫生活 孩子
You really do have the life, son.
没家庭负累
No family,
没宗教信仰
no commitments.
啊 无牵无挂
Ah, to be free of attachments.
我是个有福之人
I'm a blessed man, sir.
不 能有你这个员工
No, it is I who am blessed
我才是有福之人
to have you in my employ.
为有你这个股肱之臣 来 喝一杯
A drink to celebrate your indispensability.
这可是你珍藏了60年的威士忌啊 Charles
That's your 60-year-old Scotch, Charles.
跟你相比 这算得了什么
Nothing's too good for you.
干杯
Slaninte.
你是Hume先生?
Mr. Hume?
没错
That's right.
保释金已付齐
Bail's all been taken care of.
请记得 他不能离开本州
Remember, he's not allowed to leave the state.
Pace先生 我是Desmond Hume
Mr. Pace, I'm Desmond Hume.
Charles Widmore派我来...
Charles Widmore sent me...
嘿
Hey.
你去哪儿?
Where you going?
他归你管了
He's all yours.
嘿!
Hey!
嘿! 你有毛病啊?!
Hey! What's wrong with you?!
拜托
Come on.
给我来杯跟他一样的
Yeah, I'll have whatever he's having.
就一杯 喝完就走
One drink, then we go.
你的工作就是... 来照看我的?
So what's your job then...  to babysit me?
你是什么啊? Widmore先生的首席男佣?
What are you? Mr. Widmore's chief lackey?
侍从?
Henchman?
没头衔的
No title.
但待遇很高
Plenty of perks, though.
嗯 比如?
Mm. Such as?
我得去见形形色色的人
I get to meet charming people.
不错啊... 干杯
Well... Cheers, then.
告诉我 小侍从 你幸福吗?
Tell me, perky. Are you happy?
当然
Quite.
不 你不幸福
No, you're not.
我有一份很好的工作 有很多钱
Well, I've got a great job, lots of money,
能周游世界 我怎么会不幸福呢?
Travel the world. Why wouldn't I be happy?
- 你谈过恋爱吗?  - 谈过好多次呢
- Have you ever been in love?  - Dozens of times.
我不是说这个
That's not what I'm talking about.
我是说那种磅礴的 足以令人焕然一新的恋爱
I'm talking about spectacular, consciousness-altering love.
你知道那是什么样的吗?
Do you know what that looks like?
我不知道那会是什么样的
I wasn't aware that love looked like anything.
伙计 我见过... 就在从悉尼回来的飞机上
I've seen it, mate...  on the plane back from Sydney.
就是那样的吗?
Is that so?
我们坐的是同一个航班 所以...
Well, we were on the same flight, so...
或许我也看到过
maybe I saw it, too.
相信我 你肯定没见过
Trust me. You didn't.
没有吗? 那你教教我喽
No? Enlighten me.
有个女的
There was this woman
坐在我前面两排... 带着手铐...
two rows in front of me...  in handcuffs...
和一个警察坐在一起
sittin' with a cop.
他看着我
He looked at me,
知道我持有毒品
knew I was holding.
要是我没有采取行动 我就要被抓起来了
If I didn't take action, I'd be caught.
所以我站起来 去了洗手间...
So I got up, went to the lav...
打算把那些小袋子
proceeded to eliminate the evidence
吞下去 以销毁罪证
by swallowing my stash.
就在那个时候
And at that exact moment,
我们遇到了气流
we hit turbulence.
我便呛到了
I choked.
一整袋海洛因 卡在了我的喉咙里
The entire bag of heroin is stuck in my throat.
呃 这下惨了 我眼前一黑
It's, uh, it's over. Everything starts to go dark.
便滑进了一个深渊 然后...
I'm slippin' into the abyss, and then...
我看见了... 她
I see... her.
"她"?
"Her"?
一个女人
A woman.
金发碧眼
Blonde.
美若天仙
Rapturously beautiful.
我认识她
And I know her.
我们在一起
We're together.
就像...
It's like...
一直在一起 并且...
You've always been, and...
永远会在一起
always will be.
这种...
This...
感觉 这种...
feeling, this...
爱情
love.
正当我快迷醉的时候
And just as I'm about to be engulfed by it.
我睁开双眼
I open my eyes,
那个蠢货
and this sodding idiot
站在那儿 问我有没有事
is standing there, asking me if I'm okay.
但我确实看到了
But I saw it.
就那么一会 我看到那副景象了
Just for a moment, I saw what it looked like.
就像是...
Well, that's just...
一首诗 哥们
poetry, brother.
你应该... 为它谱一首曲子
You know, you should... you should write a song about that.
对 对 对 对 我知道你什么意思
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah. I know what you're saying.
"可怜的想自杀的摇滚明星"
"Poor suicidal rock star."
但我见到了一些真实的东西 我见到了真相
But I've seen something real. I've seen the truth.
不 那不是真相
No, that's not the truth.
你想知道真相吗 Pace?
You wanna know the real truth, Pace?
现在你可以选择
Right now you have a choice.
要么继续喝酒 要么你跟我走
You can keep on drinkin', or you can come with me.
在你做出选择之前 你要知道 如果你留在这儿
Now before you make your choice, realize that if you stay here,
那结果就会像是
it will very likely result
你的音乐生涯终结那样
in the extermination of your musical career.
如果我跟你走呢?
And if I go with you?
只要二十分钟
20 minutes,
你就能在一家五星级酒店里享福啦
you'll be luxuriating in a five-star hotel,
就在前面的海港那儿 Charles Widmore
right on the harbor front. Charles Widmore,
这座城市中最有权势的人之一
one of the most powerful men in this town,
会请你帮个忙
will owe you favor.
看上去没得选嘛
Doesn't really seem like a choice.
天无绝人之路 哥们
There's always a choice, brother.
# 芸芸众生 #
# You all, everybody #
- # 芸芸众生 #  - 那是我的乐队
- # You all, everybody #  - That's my band.
- # 貌似愚蠢 #  - 驱动轴
- # Acting like you're stupid people #  - Drive shaft.
- 我们的第一支单曲  - # 衣着昂贵 #
- Our first single.  - # Wearing expensive clothes #
每件事的开端都那么完美
The beginning of everything great.
# 芸芸众生 #
# You all, everybody #
你喜欢吗?
You like it?
- # 芸芸众生 #  - 当然 唱得挺好
- # You all, everybody #  - Sure. For what it is.
我为你感到可惜 伙计
I feel sorry for you, mate.
你觉得你很幸福 觉得你拥有了一切
You think you're happy. You think you got it all.
这就是... 你的生活
This... your life.
但事实并非如此
But you don't.
嗯 为什么 难道这一切都不是真的?
Hmm. Why, because none of it's real?
# 芸芸众生... #
# You all... #
这样好了 Hume先生 我给你一个选择 怎么样?
All right, Mr. Hume. How about I offer you a choice?
什么选择?
What's that?
要么我给你展示一下我所说的幻象
I can either show you what I'm talking about,
要么你下车
or you can get out of the car.
你怎么觉得我会下...
Why in god's name would I want to get out of...
Charlie啊! Charlie啊!
Charlie! Charlie!
别这样!
Come on!
不是Penny的船
来人啊！
Come on!
来人啊!
来人啊 该死!
Come on, damn it!
你在事故中 受到严重撞击
You sustained a pretty bad bump in your accident.
感到恶心吗?
Any nausea?
不
Nope.
- 视像有重影吗?  - 没有
- Double vision?  - No.
听着 我要找到我带过来的那个男的
Listen, I need to find the man that I was brought in here with.
有幻觉吗?
How about hallucinations?
你指什么?
What do you mean?
幻觉 看到了一些并不存在的东西
Hallucinations. Seeing things that aren't there.
呃...
Um...
我不知道
I'm not sure.
你的CAT扫描没有结论
Well, your C.A.T. scan was inconclusive.
我送你下楼 去做一个核磁共振
I'm gonna send you downstairs for an M.R.I.
不 我没空做这个
No, I don't have time for this.
- 我要找到我带过来的那个男的  - 在我们确诊你脑部情况之前
- I need to find the man I came in here with.  - I'm afraid you're not finding anyone
恐怕你是找不到任何人的
till we know what's going on inside your brain.
你佩戴了金属制品吗 比如钥匙或者链子?
Are you wearing any metal, carrying keys or chains?
在你体内有什么金属制品吗... 起搏器 针 子弹?
Any metal inside your body...  pacemakers, pins, bullets?
- 在你的头里有钢板吗?  - 不 没有
- Steel plate inside of your head?  - No, nothing.
我发现你没填紧急联系人名单
I see you didn't list an emergency contact.
没有朋友或者家属吗?
No friends or family?
呃...
Um...
就写我老板的名字吧... Charles Widmore
Just put down my employer...  Charles Widmore.
这机器很吵
This machine is super loud.
你要戴上这个
You're gonna want these.
还有这个开关
And you need the button.
- 开关?  - 应急开关
- Button?  - Panic button.
你要停下来的话 就按一下 但尽量不要按
You need to stop, press it. But try not to,
因为那样我们就得重来一遍了
'cause we'll have to start all over again from the beginning.
我会在那边那个小房间里
I'll be in that booth over there.
你听得到我的 三十分钟 准备好了吗?
You'll be able to hear me. 30 minutes, okay?
好了 我们开始吧
Okay, here we go.
不是Penny的船
Desmond啊?
Desmond?
嘿!
Hey!
嘿 让我出去!
Hey, let me out of here!
嘿!
Hey!
- 怎么了? 你没事吧?  - 我要找到我带过来的那个人
- What happened, man? Are you all right?  - I need to find the man I came in here with.
我要找到我带过来的那个人
I need to find the man I came in here with.
他叫Charlie Pace 他是一小时前来这儿的
His name is Charlie Pace. He came in an hour ago.
- 你只要给我他的房间号就...  - 如果你不是家属的话 那就无可奉告了
- If you'd just give me his room number...  - If you're not a relative, that's confidential information.
我们是一起出的事 我要见他
Look, we were in an accident together. I need to see him.
对不起 先生 实在帮不了你
Sorry, sir. There's nothing I can do.
嘿
Hey.
打扰一下
E... excuse me.
呃... 我们在大洋航空的那架飞机上见过面
Um... We were on the same Oceanic flight.
呃 从悉尼来的
Um, from Sydney.
是的 没错 你是 呃 你是坐我旁边的那个
Yeah, yeah. You were, uh, you were sitting next to me.
- Desmond 对吧?  - 没错 是的
- Desmond, right?  - Yeah, that's right.
能不能帮帮我 哥们
Listen, I-I wonder if you can help me, brother.
我要找个人 他也是我们那次航班上的
I need to find someone. He was on our plane.
- 他现在在医院  - 等等 他跟我们同一航班
- He's somewhere in the hospital.  - Wait. He was on our plane,
现在却在这个医院里?
and now he's here in the hospital?
- 全都无关紧要了! 全都无关紧要了!  - 不! 先生 求你了! 停下来!
- None of this matters! None of this matters!  - No! Sir, please! Stop!
不要激动
Take it easy.
- 你为什么要跑啊?  - 这里没人能帮得了我 让我走吧
- Why you running?  - 'Cause no one here can help me. Now let me go.
- 你为什么想要杀我啊?  - 我没想要杀你啊
- Why'd you try and kill me?  - I didn't try and kill you.
我只是想给你看点东西
I was trying to show you something.
- 你想让我看点东西? 让我看你的手  - 什么?
- You wanna show me something? Show me your hand.  - What?
你的手 给我看看你血淋淋的手
Your hand. Show me your bloody hands now.
你看到了什么 是吗?
You saw something, didn't you?
在水里的时候
In the water.
是什么?
What was it?
你在找什么 伙计?
What are you looking for, mate?
Penny是谁?
Who's Penny?
我不知道
I don't know.
啊
Ah.
- 你感觉到了 是吗?  - 我什么也没感觉到
- You felt it, didn't you? I didn't feel anything.
- 那你为什么 要对一个穿着便袍的人搭讪?  - 好了 别闹了 我们走吧
- Then why are you accosting a man in a dressing gown?  - All right, come on. We're leaving.
哇哦！你觉得我在经历这一切之后 还会开一场摇滚音乐会?
Whoa! You think I'm gonna go play a rock concert after this?
这都不重要
This doesn't matter.
统统不重要
None of this matters.
重要的是 我们都有那种感觉
All that matters is that we felt it.
你要想阻止我? 祝你好运喽
You wanna try and stop me? Good luck.
嘿 你要去哪儿?
Hey. Where you going?
如果我是你 我就不再来担心我
If I were you, I'd stop worrying about me
而要去找Penny了
and start looking for Penny.
什么叫他走了?
What do you mean he's gone?
他撞倒了急救推车旁的一个医生
He knocked over a doctor with a bloody crash cart
- 接着就跑出了医院  - 你就让他这么走了?
- and then ran out of hospital.  - And you let him go?
他是个把我车开到海里去的瘾君子 Charles
He's a junkie who drove my car into the ocean, Charles.
- 顺便告诉你 我没事 谢谢  - 你能活着我很高兴 Desmond
- I'm fine, by the way. Thanks for asking.  - And I'm thrilled you survived, Desmond.
但我吩咐你一件事的时候 我希望你能干好它
But when I give you a job to do, I expect you to do it.
- 恕我直言 先生 这不过是一场音乐会  - 我跟你说 Desmond
- With all due respect, sir, it's just a bloody concert.  - I'll tell you what, Desmond.
如果你不能把Pace带来的话
If you can't deliver Pace,
你不如自己去跟Widmore夫人说 这不过是一场音乐会吧?
why don't you tell Mrs. Widmore it's only a bloody concert?
Hume先生
Mr. Hume.
你还没见过老板的妻子 是吧?
So you've never met the boss's wife, huh?
是的
No.
祝你好运
Good luck.
请你告诉我
Please tell me how it is
你们的工作人员 怎么会没有注意到
that someone in your line of work is not aware
黄油刀是朝右摆的?
that the butter knife is placed handle to the right?
- 刀锋要像这样朝左  - 好的
- Blade facing left just so.  - Okay.
真要命
For god sake.
您是Widmore夫人吗?
Mrs. Widmore?
什么事?
Yes?
我叫Desmond Hume 我替您的丈夫工作
My name is Desmond Hume. I work for your husband.
哦 我知道了 Hume先生
Oh, of course, Mr. Hume.
Charles时常跟我提起你
Charles has told me so much about you.
我们之前居然没见过面
It's a travesty we haven't met before.
现在终于有机会了
Well, it's about time.
我深有同感 Widmore夫人
Well, the feeling is mutual, Mrs. Widmore.
哦 别这样 叫我Eloise就可以了
Oh, please. It's Eloise.
Eloise啊
Eloise.
呃 是什么风让Charles
So, uh, what crisis forced Charles
把他最得力的助手
to send his best fix-it man
吹到慈善舞会上来了?
into the bowels of charity balls?
Eloise 呃...
Well, Eloise, um...
我深感抱歉
I'm deeply sorry,
但似乎 呃 "驱动轴"乐队
but it appears as if, uh, Drive Shaft
不能和贵公子同台演出了
won't be able to perform alongside your son.
对此 呃 这都是我的责任...
And, um, I take full responsibility...
不用为此担心
Don't worry about it.
您说什么?
Excuse me?
我儿子会理解的
Oh, my son will understand.
我觉得 假如有人雇用了所谓的摇滚明星
I suppose if one employs so-called rock stars,
说不准会发生些什么事呢
a certain unpredictability comes with the territory.
是的 您... 您不生气吗?
Yeah. Y... you're not angry?
哦 亲爱的 我一点都不生气
Oh, not at all, dear.
所有事情都是注定的
What happened, happened.
Hume先生 非常感谢你
Thank you so much, Mr. Hume,
能亲自来告诉我这些事
For coming and telling me in person.
- 非常高兴见到你  - 我也是 谢谢你
- A pleasure meeting you.  - And you. Thank you.
请把那些插花放在中间
Uh, center that flower arrangement, please.
祝您有个愉快的夜晚
Have a good evening.
谢谢你
Thank you.
Leifer, Stephanie... 加二人
Leifer, Stephanie... plus two.
Markey, Mary... 加一人
Markey, Mary... plus one.
Milton, Penny... 独自来
Milton, Penny... solo.
Pepper, Nicholas... 加一人
Pepper, Nicholas... plus one.
不好意思
Excuse me.
打扰一下 呃...
I'm sorry. Um...
你刚才有念到"Penny"这个人吗?
Did you just say "Penny"?
- 你是哪位?  - 喔 我是为Widmore先生办事的 我可以看一下那个名单吗?
- And who are you?  - Um, I work for Mr. Widmore. May I see the list?
你当然不能看了
You absolutely may not.
这个名单是保密的
That list is confidential.
请原谅
Begging your pardon,
我整天都在跟绝密的文件打交道...
I... I'm entrusted with confidential items every day...
你是在质疑我吗?
Are you questioning me?
不敢 我... 仅仅是想看下那个名单而已
No, I... just want to look at one name on that list.
- 如果有什么原因 不方便让我查看...  - 跟我来
- And if, for some reason, that's a problem...  - Come with me.
所有人都出去 马上
Out, everyone. Now.
是这样的 我...
Look, I'm...
如果我越权了 我向您道歉 但是我仅仅...
I'm sorry if I've overstepped my bounds, but I just...
住嘴吧 Hume
Stop talking, Hume.
我已经很清楚你在说什么了 现在你听我说
I've heard what you've had to say. Now you listen to me.
我要你停下来
I want you to stop.
停下来? 停... 停下来什么?
Stop? S... stop what?
很明显 已经有人影响到了你对事物的看法
Someone has clearly affected the way you see things.
这是个很严重的问题 事实上 这是种侵害
This is a serious problem. It is, in fact, a violation.
所以不管你现在在做什么
So whatever you're doing,
也不管你想要追寻什么
whatever it is you think you're looking for...
你需要停下你追寻的脚步
you need to stop looking for it.
Widmore女士...
Do you...
你知道我是在追寻什么吗?
do you know what I'm looking for, Mrs. Widmore?
我找不到你还需要去追寻其它东西的理由
I don't know why you're looking for anything.
你有完美的人生
You have the perfect life.
至关重要的是 你已经得到了
On top of it, you've managed to attain
你最渴望的东西...
the thing you wanted more than anything...
那就是我丈夫的赞许
My husband's approval.
您是如何得知我需要什么的?
How do you know what I want?
我就是知道
Because I bloody do.
我需要看看那个名单...
I need to see that list...
除非你告诉我 为什么我不能看
Or you need to tell me why I can't.
Desmond 你不能看 是因为你还没有准备好
You can't because you're not ready yet, Desmond.
准备好?
Ready?
准备好? 为... 什么而做好准备?
Ready? R... ready for what?
感觉不爽吧?
That bad, huh?
车里有酒吗?
Is there any alcohol in this car?
喔 有的
Oh, yeah.
应有尽有
Whatever you need.
那么...
So, uh...
Hume先生 我们前往哪里?
Where to, Mr. Hume?
George 你就随便开开吧
Just drive, George.
- Hume先生  - 什么事?
- Mr. Hume.  - Yes?
我的名字叫Daniel Widmore
My name is Daniel. Daniel Widmore.
我们谈谈吧
We need to talk.
听着 Widmore先生 这个...
Look, uh, Mr. Widmore, um...
Dan 直接叫我Dan就好了
Dan. Please, call me Dan.
"Widmore先生"是我父亲
"Mr. Widmore" is my father.
Dan 是这样的 如果... 如果是关于Charlie Pace
Dan, um, look, if... if this is about Charlie Pace
无法和你同台演出这件事
not being able to perform with you,
我... 我表示遗憾
I'm... I'm very sorry.
Hume先生 你相信一见钟情吗?
Do you believe in love at first sight, Mr. Hume?
你说什么?
Excuse me?
几周前 我路过这家博物馆的时候
The first time I saw her, I was walking through this museum
第一次见到了她
a few weeks ago.
她... 她就在这里工作 那时她正好午餐休息
She... she works here. She was on her lunch break.
她正在吃一个巧克力棒
She was eating a chocolate bar.
她拥有蓝宝石般的眼睛 红色的头发
She has these incredible blue, blue eyes, red hair.
就在我看到她的时候
And as soon as I saw her,
就在... 在那个瞬间 就像...
right... right in that moment, it was like...
仿佛我已经爱上了她
it was like I already loved her.
事情也从那刻起 变得诡异了起来
And that's when things got weird.
在我见到那个女人的当晚...
That same night after I saw that woman...
我忽然醒来 并且写了这些
I woke up and I wrote this.
这是什么呢?
So what is it?
我也不知道 我仅仅是个搞音乐的
I'm a musician. I have no idea.
然后我把这个 给一个加州理工学院的朋友看
So I took it to a friend of mine at Caltech.
他精通数学 他说这个是量子力学
He's a math whiz. He said this is quantum mechanics.
他说这些方程式非常超前
He said these equations are so advanced that
只有那些研究了一辈子物理的人
only someone who'd been studying physics their entire life
才可以想出来
could've come up with them.
所以...
So...
所以 那意味着什么?
so what do they mean?
好吧 想象一下... 假如一桩恐怖事件
Okay, imagine... imagine something terrible is about to happen,
一件惨事即将发生
something catastrophic.
唯一可以阻止这件事情发生
And the only way to stop it from happening
的办法是...
was by...
释放一股巨大的能量
releasing a huge amount of energy.
就比如引爆原子弹
Like setting off a nuclear bomb.
你想要去引爆原子弹?
You wanna set off a nuclear bomb?
听着 如果这些... 所有这些...
Just listen. What if this... all this...
假如所有的这些 都不应该是我们的宿命呢?
what if this wasn't supposed to be our life?
假如... 我们本可以有别的生活
What if we... we had some other life
可是出于某些原因 生活的轨迹被更改了?
and for some reason, we changed things?
Hume先生 我不想去引爆原子弹
I don't want to set off a nuclear bomb, Mr. Hume.
可是 我想我已经这么做了
I think I already did.
听着 伙计...
Listen, mate, um...
我不知道这些事情与我有什么关系 所以...
I don't know what any of this has to do with me. So...
你为什么要问我妈妈 那个叫Penny的女孩子?
Why did you ask my mother about a woman named Penny?
你有过一见钟情 对不?
It happened to you, too, didn't it?
你有这种感觉
You felt it.
我不知道...
I don't know...
我自己也不清楚我的感受
I don't know what I felt.
是的 你感觉到了
Yes, you do.
你感受到了爱
You felt love.
那是不可能的
That's impossible because
因为我对这个女人一无所知
I don't know anything about this woman.
我不知道... 我不知道她身在何方
I don't know... I don't know where she is.
我甚至不知道 她是否活在这世上
I don't even know if she exists.
她是...
She's...
她只是我凭空想出来的
She's an idea.
你错了 Hume先生
No, Mr. Hume.
她是我的同父异母的姐妹
She's my half-sister.
我可以很清楚地告诉你 你可以在何时何地找到她
And I can tell you exactly where and when you can find her.
打扰一下?
Excuse me?
什么事?
Yeah?
你是Penny?
Are you Penny?
呃 是的
Uh, yes.
你好
Hello.
我叫Desmond
I'm Desmond.
呃 你好
Uh, hi.
赶紧检查下
Checking in now.
他没事
He's okay.
确实 他没事
Indeed he is.
Desmond 你好吗? 你感觉如何?
How are you, Desmond? How are you feeling?
挺好的
Fine.
我... 我昏迷了多久?
H... how long was I unconscious for?
不过几秒钟而已
Oh, no more than a few seconds.
你可以把我拉起来吗?
Will you help me up, please?
Desmond 很抱歉我们对你做的这一切
I'm really sorry we had to do this to you, Desmond.
但是正如我所说的 你的... 天赋是我们任务成败的关键
But as I told you, your... talent is vital to our mission.
所以如果你需要我给你解释...
So if you just let me explain...
没关系 我可以理解
It's all right. I understand.
什么?
What?
我说我可以理解的
I said I understand.
你告诉过我 说你把我带到岛上
You told me you brought me here to the island
去完成一些非常重要的事情
to do something very important.
是的
Yeah.
我们什么时候开工?
When do we start?
你怎么了?
What happened to you?
什么意思?
What do you mean?
我是说 20分钟以前
What I mean is 20 minutes ago,
你用输液架冲着Widmore一通乱打
you were beating the crap out of Widmore with an I.V. Stand,
然而... 然而现在 你却对他言听计从
and... and now you're Mr. Cooperative.
士别三日 当刮目相看嘛
A lot can happen in 20 minutes.
确实是
Sure it can.
肯定是你的脑袋被烧坏了
That thing fried your brain.
是吗?
Did it?
无论如何 你终究还是会...
Whatever. Doesn't change that you're gonna...
快滚
Run.
Desmond 我没有时间给你解释
Desmond, I don't have time to explain,
但是这些人都是非常危险的
but these people are extremely dangerous.
我们现在必须赶紧走了
We need to go now.
嗯 当然
Aye, of course.
你带路吧
Lead the way.
喂? 你还好吗?
Hello? You okay?
发生什么事了?
What happed?
喔 我握了下你的手 然后你就晕过去了
Well, I shook your hand, and then you fainted.
我肯定把你迷晕了
I must have quite an effect on you.
是的
Aye.
是的 你真迷人
Aye, you must have.
我们以前见过吗?
Have we met before?
我... 我觉得如果我们俩见过面 肯定会记得的
I... I think we'd remember it if we have
对的
Yeah.
好吧 只要你确定你现在没事了...
Well, as long as you're sure you're all right...
是的 我很好
Yeah, I'm fine.
嘿 听着 呃...
Hey, listen. Um...
你愿意跟我去喝杯咖啡吗?
Would you like to go for a coffee?
什么 现在?
What, now?
我一身臭汗的
I'm a sweaty mess.
我刚刚都晕倒在你的面前了
I just fainted in front of you.
就当我们扯平了
I'd say we're even.
在Sweetzer和Melrose的交叉口
There's a coffee shop
有家咖啡店
on the corner of Sweetzer and Melrose.
我们一个小时后在那里见
I'll meet you there in an hour.
好的
Absolutely.
- 好的  - 一会见
- Okay.  - Okay.
所以... 你有找到你想找的东西吗?
So... did you find what you were looking for?
是的 George 我找到了
Yes, George, I did.
咱们到Melrose和Sweetzer的交叉口
Corner of Melrose and Sweetzer, please.
这就出发
You got it.
Hume先生 如果您还有什么需要我帮忙的
And if there's anything else I can do for you, Mr. Hume,
尽管开口就好了
you just name it.
George 其实 还真有个事要你帮忙
Actually, there is one thing, George.
你可以帮我弄到 我从悉尼来的那趟航班的 乘客名单吗?
Can you get me the manifest from my flight from Sydney?
大洋航空 815航班
Oceanic 815.
只要乘客的姓名就好了
Just the names of the passengers.
没问题 我可以弄到
Sure, I can.
您介意我问问 您要那个名单做什么吗?
Do you mind if I ask you what you need it for?
我仅仅是想给他们看点东西
I just need to show them something.